{
   "response_code": 0,
   "results": [
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Who was the person after whom Stanford University was named when it was founded in 1891?",
         "correct_answer": "Leland Stanford Jr.",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Jane Lathrop Stanford",
            "Governor Leland Stanford",
            "Stanford White"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": " What property did the Stanford family use on which to build the campus?",
         "correct_answer": "Their horse breeding farm",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Near the governor's mansion",
            "Acreage overlooking the Pacific Ocean",
            "An abandoned mission church"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Which Stanford varsity football player won the Heisman Trophy in 1970?",
         "correct_answer": "Jim Plunkett",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "James Lofton",
            "Toby Gereasyt",
            "Andrew Luck"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "What was the name of the Stanfords' pet cat whose name lives on in a popular local restaurant?",
         "correct_answer": "Tootsie",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Footsie",
            "Bootsie",
            "Cutsie"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Stanford's free Marguerite Shuttle service is named for Jane Stanford's favorite horse.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Stanford has always been a co-educational institution.",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Which of these US Presidents attended Stanford?",
         "correct_answer": "Herbert Hoover and John F. Kennedy",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Only Hoover",
            "Riceasy Nixon",
            "Ronald Reagan"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "What architect designed both the Stanford University campus and Central Park in New York City?",
         "correct_answer": "Frederick Law Olmsted",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "I.M. Pei",
            "Birge Clark",
            "Stanford White"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Which presidential offspring graduated from Stanford in 2001?",
         "correct_answer": "Chelsea Clinton",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Michael Reagan",
            "Amy Carter",
            "Jenna Bush"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "What is the name of the official Stanford Cardinal fight song?",
         "correct_answer": "Come Join The Band",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Victorious Cardinal",
            "For Old Cardinal",
            "All Right Now"

         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The Stanford University Marching Band bills itself as what?",
         "correct_answer": "The World's Largest Rock and Roll Band",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "The Pride of the West",
            "The Marching Cardinal",
            "The Wind of the Cardinal"

         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Who did the Stanford Cardinal hire as their head football coach in 2011?",
         "correct_answer": "David Shaw",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "John Elway",
            "Tyrone Willingham",
            "Cliff Clavin"

         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Before each home game, the Stanford football team walk past cheering fans from the AFSC to the stadium, in this tradition commonly known as?",
         "correct_answer": "The Walk",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "The Stanford Stomp",
            "The Cardinal March",
            "Stanford Stride"

         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "What is the name of the unofficial Stanford Cardinal mascot?",
         "correct_answer": "Stanford Tree",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "Cardy the Cardinal",
            "Pops",
            "Stan"

         ]
      },
      {
         "category": "location",
         "type": "multiple",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Stanford's motto appears on the University Seal: 'Die luft der freiheit weht.' What does this mean?",
         "correct_answer": "The wind of freedom blows",
         "incorrect_answers": [
            "The light of freedom shines",
            " Learning leads to freedom",
            "The life of freedom is heavy"
         ]
      }
   ]
}
